(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Many people think that it is very important
to make a lot of backlinks to bring
reserves in off-page SEO.
Let's see a student's study on how he
followed our high-quality off-page SEO framework
and brought more than 1 million impressions and
11,000 clicks on his website in just
a few months.
And how you can implement this thing.
Meet our amazing student Hassan, who learned off
-page SEO properly and implemented the strategy properly.
And brought more than 1 million impressions and
11,000 clicks on his website in just
a few months.
Learn these three things well, then you can
also get good results from off-page SEO.
Number 1.
Clean Anchor Text Never just use your keywords
as anchor text and generate all the backlinks.
Instead, distribute them properly.
Use branded, naked URLs, generic words, and related
keywords together as anchor text so that you
don't leave your footprints and Google and other
search engines can't penalise you.
Number 2.
Different Backlinks Techniques Never just follow one technique
and make all the backlinks.
Because this way you are telling Google to
hit you.
When you follow the same technique and make
all the backlinks, you are signalling Google that
I am trying to manipulate you.
That's why always keep your backlink profile natural
and clean.
Number 3.
Proper URL Distribution Remember, never give all the
backlinks to just one page of your website.
Instead, distribute them to different pages in some
blog posts.
So that link juice can also pass those
pages.
They can also help in ranking and at
the same time make your profile clean and
natural.
That's why I always tell my students that
more than the quantity of backlinks, their quality
and their way of generation matters.
Tell me in the comments below what issues
you are facing in off-page SEO.
I will also clear them.
If you want to see more such live
student case studies, then follow me and share
this reel.
Thank you.